<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">Coptic tourism</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="Mena">Mena Ayman</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="Pyra1">The hanging Church</string>
    <string name="loc1">Ancient Egypt</string>
    <string name="loc2">Alexandria</string>
    <string name="loc3">The Red Sea</string>
    <string name="loc4">ElBeheira</string>
    <string name="Cairo_abbasiya_mark_head">The Coptic Orthodox Coptic Cathedral</string>
    <string name="loc_Cairo_abbasiya_mark">Abbasid,Cairo</string>
    <string name="saint_katreen_head">Catherine Monastery</string>
    <string name="loc_saint_katreen">South of Sinai</string>
    <string name="Deir_Almoharraq_head">Monastery of Moharraq Assiut</string>
    <string name="loc_Deir_Almoharraq">Qusiya,Assiut</string>
    <string name="Deir_Maryam_Mostorod_head">Monastery of the Virgin Mary Maryam</string>
    <string name="loc_Deir_Maryam_Mostorod">cairo,Mostorod</string>
    <string name="Deir_vergin_maddi_head">Monastery of the Virgin Mary in Maddi</string>
    <string name="Deir_Maryam_Badranek_Assiut_head">Deir Maryam Badranek Assiut</string>
    <string name="loc_Deir_Maryam_Badranek_Assiut">Badranek,Assiut</string>
    <string name="loc_eir_vergin_maddi">Elmaddi</string>
    <string name="locDeir7banat">South Sinai </string>
    <string name="Deirel7banat_head">Deir Seven Girls</string>
    <string name="chu1">The Church of the Virgin Mughas</string>
    <string name="Sergio">Abi Serija Church</string>
    <string name="Mark">Mark Church</string>
    <string name="baramus_head">Al -Baramus Monastery</string>
    <string name="Antonios_head">Monastery of St. Anthony</string>
    <string name="bola_head">Monastery of St. Paula</string>
    <string name="Syriaan_head">Deir Al Syriaan</string>
    <string name="bishoy_head">Monastery of St. Bishoy</string>
    <string name="Abo_mena_head">Abu Mina archaeological area</string>
    <string name="Marmemina_head">Marmina Al Ajabi</string>
    <string name="the_hanging_Church"> The suspended church is located in the ancient neighborhood of Egypt, in the important  archaeological area Others. And it was called the spoon because it was built on two towers from the ancient towers of the Romanian fortress (Babylon Fort), which was built by Emperor Trajan in the second century AD, and the hanging is the oldest church that still remains in Egypt.
    </string>
    <string name="chu">The Church of the Virgin, Haret Al -Rum (Church of the Virgin Al -Mughaeth) in Cairo, Egypt. The creation of this church was started in the late fifth or early sixth century AD. Its architecture was in the middle of the aforementioned century during the reign of Pope Arsius I. However, it was destroyed, so he ordered it to be closed in 1026 AD.
After the Pope Khrstoulals, he moved from the St. Mark\'s Church in Alexandria to Egypt, and he took the Church of Hanging on the apparent of Al -Fustat as his headquarters. He also renewed the Church of St. Merbarosus and made it a major cathedral and center of his chairs, and also made the Church of the Virgin Mary in the Arwam neighborhood as his shelter when necessary, with the consent of Babilon\'s bishop. The reason for this is the transfer of the greatness of Alexandria to the city of Cairo, the large number of Christians in it, and its association with the government. So the Pope appointed a bishop for Alexandria in the name of the agent of the St. Mark.
Pope Mutawas IV was the last of the Patriarchal frying pan in the Zouila neighborhood because he transferred his chair to the Church of the Virgin Mary, the Roman neighborhood in the year 1660 AD, the first days of his painting. In the year 1800 AD, in the eighth days of Paphmarks, the Patriarchate Center moved from the Roman neighborhood to the St. Mark\'s Cathedral in Azquar … the church building
 It drops from the level of street land by approximately and a half meters. The church architecture consists of a facility on the name of Prince Tadros al -Mashriqi, which includes a monastery of the nuns and two churches, one of them for the Virgin and the other to Mar Gerges.

The Church of the Virgin Mary includes a southern interface in the middle of the entrance, which is a rectangular door opening with a wooden shutter from combined fillings adorned with simple geometric shapes. The door leads to a plate, two wings and three structures, covered by a roof consisting of twelve dome, three of which are above the structures, and widespread over the plate and wings. This courtyard is separated from the entrance monsters with five pillars, and it has a platform with a spiral wooden ladder based on the northern pillar of the place of the pillars. Part of the floors of this part of the church has brushed with a new wood, while the other part remained furnished with old stone tiles.</string>


<string name="sergio">
    The archaeological Church of Abi Serija or the Church of the two martyrs, Sargius and Akhs, is the archaeological church built over the place where the Holy Family was set up during the flight of escape and has a cave of escape at the temple. And its current location is what is known as the Synod of Religions in Old Cairo, inside the Babylon Fort near the Bani Al -Hadra Al -Jewish (between him and the Barbara Church).
 Deotified Sargius and Bacchus, who were martyred during the fourth century in Syria by the Roman Emperor Maximian. The most interesting advantage is the cellar, as it is said that Maryam, Youssef and the child Jesus are said. The depth of the cellar is 10 meters, and when the levels of the Nile rises, the water is often flooded. The church was built in the fourth century and may have been completed during the fifth century. It was burned during the Fustat fire during the reign of Marwan II. However, it is still considered a model for early Coptic churches. Again, there are the most valuable and oldest icons on the southern wall. A wide central hall divided into three tiles with two rows of columns.
By the eleventh century AD, the headquarters of the Pope of Alexandria, the Coptic Orthodox, was transferred historically in Alexandria, Egypt to Cairo, where the ruling authorities moved from Alexandria to Cairo after the Arab invasion of Egypt and during the period of the rule of Pope Kristodolus in Cairo. The fixed and official headquarters of the Coptic Pope in the suspended church in Cairo became in 1047.
</string>

    <string name="Deir_Maryam_Badranek_Assiut">
        The Monastery of the Virgin is located in the western mountain of the city of Assiut and at a height of a hundred meters from the surface of the agricultural land, and it is ten kilometers from the city that the car cuts in a quarter of an hour. The village of Darnah, then heads towards the rising road to the mountain, a kilometer, and at the end of it, the car arrives in front of the doors of the monastery. The visitor can also reach the monastery from the ring road, which starts at the 3 km three before entering the city of Assiut from the northern side and at the 4 km four from the southern side.
Christ came to him, glory to Egypt, and he is a young child with his mother, the Virgin Mary and Saint Joseph Al -Najjar. To its western mountain, where the well -known cave in which the Holy Family came to, and later, the Monastery of the Virgin, who is being sold over the chest of this mountain overlooking the Green Valley extending east to the course of the Nile, and the coming of the Holy Family was to Mount Assiut in the month of August and he is the one in which fasting The Virgin, and this is why the monastery holds its religious celebrations annually, starting from 7 August 7 to the 21st of it every year
The monastery churches
The monastery is a group of churches, the oldest of which is the Church of the Cave, and the length of it was 160 million and sixty meters and its depth is 60 sixty meters and it is since the end of the first Christian century. Roles, and have large halls for religious and social services and technical activities, and rooms for hospitality and residence.
The monastery message
The monastery has its religious message. Since the dawn of Christianity, the Christians continued to inherit the residence in it. The monastery holds the prayers and the secret of the baptism daily, and the visitors are received from six in the morning and closed its sixth gates in the evening, but the deadline extends to eleven in the evening during the month of August, while the overnight stay in the monastery will be according to a previous statement. The Monastery of the Virgin in Mount Assiut is considered one of the important tourist attractions in the Egyptian countries
Thousands of foreign and Egyptian visitors went to the year to get to know the place where the Holy Family march ended, and from it the journey of return began. The Virgin has manifested a light in a light and still appears from time to time in this blessed monastery, where people find calm, comfort, peace and pleasure.

    </string>
    <string name="Deir_Maryam_Mostorod">
        Many Egyptian and international churches were called the Virgin Mary Mary in honor of this privacy woman in the lives of the Copts and the extent of her influence on the whole world and Christians in particular, and all the churches carrying this named for the virgin holidays celebrate in particular in the Christian world.
Among the most prominent churches bearing this great name is the Church of the Virgin in Surded, due to the privacy of the historical events that this church witnessed and the monuments that every Christian Christian or immigrant intends, so this church is considered an archaeological sign of Egypt that tourists go to when they come to this country.
The Church of the Virgin Mary in Saddord of the Diocese of Shubra Al -Khaimah in Qaliubiya Governorate is the most important church, where the celebration is used as a form with the birth, and Christians come from all sides to seek the special blessing that this church enjoys, which comes from its busy history and the journey of the Holy Family in it.
This church was almost established in the twelfth century AD and it was mentioned in many books of the history of the ecclesiastical, as it is one of the stations of the Holy Family in Egypt to which it descended from the Zaqqa and is famous for the church (the male) and that name was taken by the Church after the Virgin Mary washed the child Jesus Christ and his clothes in the well existing well. This blessed well was discovered by Pope Gabriel I in 1481 and was a Jewish temple, and while the Holy Family was in Egypt, it settled for three days and used this well throughout their stay. This well is an archaeological symbol that is not only linked to Copts, as it is a source of water for all humanity. The privacy of this blessed well of Christians is to use the pure virgin lady virginity of its water, which made there believe that those who use the water of this well may be cured of disease and fatigue. And after the Holy Family entered Egypt from the east fleeing the military, it has settled a small cave inside the dome or what is now known as the arms and the child Jesus Christ blessed the land of this church, so this church has privacy among the Copts inside Egypt.

    </string>

    <string name="DeirEl7banat">
        Deir Seven Girls
Deir Al -Saba is the daughters, located in the village of Wadi Ferran, which is affiliated with the city of Abordis, in the South Sinai Governorate, an oasis of beauty and architectural and archaeological masterpiece, where greenness on each side and farms of olives and fruits depends on the water of the airport and wells.
The monastery is surrounded by very beautiful mountain ranges, and the Monastery of the Seven remains the daughters of the nuns, and the first women\'s corridor from the countries of Europe, especially Greece and Romania, to which the beautiful women of Europe offer slaves of worshipers in that spot of the blessed land surrounded by mountains from each side.
The monastery was built in the Valley of Ferran since the fourth century AD and is the first and greatest Christian center on the peninsula and was the center of the Sinai bishops. At the same time, the Monastery of Saint Catherine was built to be the headquarters for the establishment of nuns. World monasteries.
Rifaat Al -Nimr, responsible for the monastery, said in a special statement to "Al -Bawaba News": "There are currently 5 nuns, including 4 Greeks and one of Romania, headed by the nun," Janadia Bniwiti ", and there is 5 churches in the monastery other than two churches over Mount Mills surrounding the monastery."
Al -Nimr attributed the reason for naming the monastery with this name that he had lived in 7 nuns since the Roman times and were subjected to the persecution of the Romans and the attempts to attack them from the bandits and criminals, so they went up to the highest mountain of the Valley of Firan and the gun of their clothes together and threw themselves from the top of the mountain.
Dr. Abdul Rahim Rayhan, Director General of Research, Archaeological Studies and Scientific Publishing in Sinai, said that the Ferran Valley is located 60 kilos northwest of the Monastery of Saint Catherine, 5 km long and width between 250 to 375 meters.
It was characterized by the abundance of water from the wells and eyes that feed the valley gardens, and some wells of the valley were depleted, which led to the lack of water. The mountain was the place of sanctification before the journey of the exit of Israel to the Sinai.
The Valley "Ferran", an integrated Christian city discovered in Sinai, containing monuments of more than 1500 years from the fourth century to the sixth AD, witnessed the arrival of Christians to it from Europe, safe, reassured on the turquoise land on their journey to Jerusalem via Sinai, including the monk Kozmas in 535 AD, and the monk Antonius In the year 565 AD, the valley was a shelter for the first autism in Sinai, who took refuge in the oppression Girls dating back to the fifth century AD.
Rayhan stressed that the Valley of Ferran, an archaeological, tourist and environmental treasure, is not exploited until now, and it is the valley that has enjoyed the visits of European travelers since the sixth century AD.
He continued: "The beauty citizen in this valley recorded the paintings of the Greek plastic artist Elinie in Oulu, who gathered in her immortal paintings between the impact, trees, human beings and the picturesque nature."
He pointed out that the archaeological area in Valley Ferran, includes an integrated Byzantine city in the archaeological instigator and an area of ​​400 meters in length of 200 meters, which has a wall of the sixth century AD, its foundations of stone and the upper part of the mud brick, and the city includes clear -planned homes, graves on the outskirts of the city and four churches Including the Episcopal Church for the Pap for the Pontifical and the Church of the city, and part of it was allocated as a hospital, and the Archdiocese of Firan is considered the oldest Archdiocese in Sinai since 451 meters, and it had a papal seat.
He emphasized that the Viran Archdiocese moved to the Sinai Tor, the current "St. Catherine region", after the construction of the Monastery of the Sinai, which was called the Monastery of Saint Catherine in the ninth century AD of the famous story of Sant Catherine and found its remains over the top of the mountain, which was known after that.
The Sinai Archdiocese Center moved from the Valley of Firan to the Monastery of Tor Sinai 90 years after its construction, and the Monastery of Saint Catherine became a center for the diocese of the Sinai and the bishop became nicknamed "Bishop of the Monastery of Tor Sinai, Jiran and Raya", and a intentional banner with the current city of Tor Sinai.
He added that the Veran Valley contains the Mill of the Mill, facing the archaeological instigator, and is characterized by an unusual beauty and rises 886 meters above sea level. And the environment and used a mortar of love, caused by the large number of torrents, in the region, which brings this mortar to the foot of the mountain.
He pointed out that the civilizational role of this valley is still continuing until now. About this church in 1979 AD, it is characterized by the luster cypress trees as a symbol of eternity and devoted to the nuns of the Monastery of Saint Catherine and is called the Monastery of the Modern Girls.
"Rayhan" called for the benefit of the Valley of Ferran, the archaeological and natural treasure, to convert it into an open natural civilized museum that includes archaeological treasures, which confirms civilized coexistence and tolerance on the land of Egypt to stimulate cultural and religious tourism in the valley and exploit the torrents in the valley. The unique nature of mountains has a special magic that combines humans, stone and trees in one place, to stimulate environmental tourism in the valley

    </string>

    <string name="Deir_church_of_vergin_maddi">
        In the suburb of Maadi and on the beach of Nile Cairo directly, the Church of the Virgin Mary is located in its distinctive archaeological style, witnessing the journey of the Holy Family to Egypt, which was taken from its basement as a port for the family crossing through the Nile to Upper Egypt, specifically to Jabal Qassam in Assiut, where the Monastery of Muharraq is located.
Father Calem, Wadih, who took into account the church, cut to Al -Watan the history of the place he says belongs to Musa al -Nabi, who was born in the Tora region, and when Pharaoh came and wanted to kill all the children of Israel, his mother put him in “Sabbat” from the papyrus and threw it in the Nile And his sister walked next to the Nile, following him, until the daughter of Pharaoh saw the "Saturday" in the position of the Church of the Virgin currently, which was taking a shower area in the Nile, and she was the name of "Moses" and meaning "Ibn Al -Nile", and he took advantage of this place until the birth of Christ when he commanded "Herod" by killing all the children of Bethlehem, so the Virgin Mary and Youssef Al -Najjar, with them Jesus, and the "blood" that the Virgin gave birth and saw with her eyes the hymen, where she became pregnant and gave birth, and she is still a virgin
"Akmrimsind" added that the Holy Family went on the way to escape to Egypt to the Church of Abu Sarjah in ancient Egypt before they arrived at the Church of the Virgin in Maadi and stayed in it on the path of escaping for 3 days while they were heading to Jabal Qasqam in Assiut (Deir al -Muharraq), and they also stayed in it while returning to a house Meat, but the period in which they stayed in that area known as the "Adawiya" area was not known, and they were the ones who possessed this land at this time, so it was called the Church and Monastery of the Virgin Mary Maryam.
Regarding the building of the church, Wadih said that Queen Helena, the mother of the Roman Emperor Constantine, who discovered the “Holy Cross” upon which Christ was crucified, asked her son to search for every place to which the Holy Family went to and built a church in the name of the Virgin Mary, and who Between these places, the Church of the Virgin Mary in Maadi was in the fourth century AD, which was repeated throughout the ages, and her last restoration in the eleventh century AD, where there was a convoy of Nile loaded with weapons and exploded in front of the church, which led to its complete destruction, and rebuilt again in the same place.
"Aklimmend": A witness to picking up "Moses" from the Nile to the Pharaoh Palace .. There are only 3 domes and 3 massacres left
Father Calemims pointed out that the church contains 3 structures and 3 domes, and it has a "well" that was drinking from the Holy Family, but this well due to the lack of purification during the recent period, the water was depleted from it, pointing out that if the well is cleared, the fresh Nile water will come out of it, Adding that the church has the shrouds of some saints, and it has an icon that tells the story of the life of the Virgin Mary from her birth until her death, and it includes the Bible with the large size since 1976 that he found the pastor of the church and called the priest Bishara on the surface of the Nile, and saturated with water and open to the travel of Isaiah Al -Mushara 19 which exists It has a verse that says: “Mubarak is the people of Egypt”, in addition to the Church containing the archaeological peace that reaches the bottom of the Nile, which is placed on it “a dome” and has a altar, and the water before the construction of the High Dam sinks the ladder and flows into the church, but after the construction of the High Dam and based on The request of the Ministry of Irrigation and Water Resources was built in front of the ladder to protect the buildings. Some of its stairs were hidden, but some drawers are still present and are used to climb and go down.
The sponsor of the church continued that in front of the church is another ladder that arrives at the Marqab of the Church and reaches the Nile, and at the end of this basement, he sees the monastery of Abu Seifin on the opposite side, and the basement was used to transport people and still exists and it was restored and a icon was placed in the Virgin and Christ.
Father Akmimsd explained that the church was completely restored in the seventies of the last century, and there are only 3 domes and 3 massacres, and tourists come to the church from everywhere, and after the decision to adopt the path of the Holy Family in Egypt, there is coordination between the Ministry of Tourism and the Church represented in the Anba Daniel, Bishop of Maadi and its dependencies to arrange for dealing with this matter
    </string>

    <string name="church_george">
        St. Georges Church or St. George Church
 It is a Greek Orthodox Church inside the Babylon Castle in Coptic Cairo. It is part of the Monastery of St. George, the Holy Patriarchate of the Orthodox Patriarchate in Alexandria and all Africa. It is the only round church in Egypt.
The date of the construction of the church
It was built in the tenth century on the top of the Roman tower with the Babylonian fort. The Church is linked to the Monastery of St. George. The Church is the headquarters of the Baba Chair and the Patriarch of the Alexandria Church of the Greek Orthodox.
The current structure was rebuilt after a fire in 1904, the construction ended in 1909, since 2009, the monastery was visited by the rank of bishop with the title of Bishop of Babylos ("Bishop of Babylon")

    </string>

    <string name="saint_katreen">
        St. Catherine Monastery
The Monastery of St. Catherine or the Monastery of St. Catherine for Holy Jerusalem is an eastern Orthodox monastery located in the Sinai Peninsula, at the mouth of a strait at the foot of Mount Sinai below Mount Catherine above the mountains in Egypt, near the city of Saint Catherine, Egypt. The monastery was named after Catherine from Alexandria.
It is said that he is the oldest monastery in the world, which is considered a great tourist attraction, as it is intended for tourist groups from all parts The name of the Patriarch of Jerusalem is mentioned in the masses, although the guardianship of the monastery was for long periods of the Russian Orthodox Church, and the monks and priests of the monastery from the Greeks and not Arabs or Egyptians, like the bishops of the Greek Orthodox Church in Jerusalem, which is controlled by the Greeks of long periods. The bishop of Sinai runs alongside the monastery churches and holy shrines in South Sinai in the Al -Tor region, Firan and Tarfa Oasis.

History of the monastery
The monastery was built on the command of Empress Helen, the mother of Emperor Constantine, but the Emperor Justinian was the one who actually built between 545 AD to contain the remains of Saint Catherine who lived in Alexandria.
The oldest record of monastic life in Mount Sinai comes from the travel magazine, which he wrote in Latin, a needy woman named Eugeia (Etharia; Saint Silvia from Akitin) around 381 / 2-386.
The monastery was built by order of Emperor Justinian I (527-565), and it contains the burning Bush chapel (also known as the “St. Helen Church”). Interesting bush. It is claimed that it is the living shrub on the ground that Moses saw. The structure of the monastery is the property of another beauty is the oldest known as the roof of the world in the world. The site is sacred to Christianity, Islam and Judaism.
During the seventh century, the accompanying of the isolated Christian Sinai was eliminated: only the fortified monastery remained. The monastery is still surrounded by the huge fortifications that have maintained it. Until the twentieth century, arrival was done through a high door in the outer walls. From the beginning of the first Crusader campaign, the presence of the Crusaders in Sinai until 1270 has caused the attention of European Christians and increased the number of bold pilgrims who visited the monastery. The monastery was supported by its dependencies in Egypt, Palestine, Syria, Crete, Cyprus and Constantinople.
Oswari in the Monastery of Saint Catherine
The monastery, in addition to many dependencies in the region, is the entire Sinai Church, which is headed by the head of bishops and is also the head of the monastery. The exact administrative status of the Church within the Eastern Orthodox Church is mysterious: by some, including the church itself, and the ecologicalk, by others, is considered by others on the autonomy of the Church under the judicial mandate of the Greek Orthodox Church Jerusalem. The bishops are traditionally perpetuated by the Jerusalem Patriarch of the Greek Orthodox; He usually stayed in Cairo in recent centuries. During the Crusades period that was bitterly characterized by the Orthodox and Catholic churches, the monastery was sponsored by both Byzantine emperors and the rulers of the Kingdom of Jerusalem and their courts.
On April 18, 2017, an attack by ISIS caused a checkpoint near the monastery to kill a policeman and wound three police officers.

    </string>

    <string name="Deir_Almoharraq">
            The Monastery of Muharraq is considered one of the paths of the Holy Family in Egypt during its flight from Bethlehem in Palestine, where the period that the family spent in this place is one of the longest periods, and the cave that the family inhabited is the first church in Egypt, but in the whole world.
            During the following lines, we publish the most prominent information about Deir al -Muharraq, one of the paths of the Holy Family.
            1 - The Monastery of the Virgin Lady is about 12 km west of the city and the Qusiya Center in Assiut.
            2 - The Holy Family stayed in the monastery for a period of "6 months and 10 days."
            3 - After the Holy Family stayed, the monastery is built, and the church of the ancient Virgin was built and the first altar in the world, which is the stone on which Christ was sitting.
            4 - His fame is due to the Monastery of Muharraq until the monastery was adjacent to the area of ​​weeds assembly and harmful plants and burning them.
            5 - He was famous for the monastery of Jabal Qassam, and Qassem is an old name since the era of the Pharaohs, and it consists of two priests …
            6 - The monastery includes the cave that the Holy Family broadcasts and the Church of the Virgin Mary, which is the oldest church in the Christian world, was built in 38 AD, the Church of Al -Hosn or the Church of the Angel Gabriel, the building in the late sixth century and the beginning of the seventh century AD.
            7 - The Church of the ancient Virgin Mary is considered an abandoned house in which the Holy Family lived and remained on its area until the 19th century, after which in the Christian era it turned into a church and was established on both sides of the Temple.
    </string>

    <string name="Marmina">
    Monastery of Marmina Al -Ajabi
It came in the book "Mimer, the Great Martyr Marmina, the wonders" of the shirt, John Al -Sobky, p. 68: To sell you

And it was stated in one of the manuscripts from St. Mar Mina Al -Ajabi that the Lord said to him: “Do not be afraid, my love .. I make a lot visiting your sale .. And I call two and seventy countries who give gifts to your sale. Sixth, p. 34

The old monastery

The remains of the martyr Marmina arrived and settled in her old shrine with the antiquities about (312 - 315 AD).
The first church of the martyr was built between the years 320 - 325 AD during the reign of King Constantine the Great.
With the increasing number of visitors and miracles, Pope Athanasius, the Apostolic Church, renewed the first church.
When the number of visitors was very many, St. Thyfelus, the Pope 23 (385 - 412 AD) built a huge cathedral east of the first church, as he renewed and expanded the first church and built in its west a great baptism.
With the fame of the saint and the increase in the number of visitors, the region turned into an important tourist city, in which the cathedrals, marble churches, and numerous facilities such as bathrooms and hotels were spread.
The number of monks increased to hundreds, a great monastery was established in the region, which was getting widespread over time. The activity of some of his monks extended to the preaching in Europe. The Irish Church maintains its prayers to this day with a special prayer for the Coptic monks who carried the flame of faith.
The city fell in its churches as an aspiration for the Khaldouni foreigners, the fabrications of the Persians, the Berbers, the Arab conquest, and the Turkish caliphs …
The martyr\'s body moved through a long journey from Mariout to his church in the mouth of the Gulf in ancient Egypt in the first half of the fourteenth century.
Muhammad Ali Pasha (1805-1848) eliminated the rest of the churches and facilities in the region to prevent looting and looting that spread in the region, as the thieves took advantage of these abandoned ruins as their dens. Then nature also ravaged to make the place piles of dirt and stones.
The archaeological disclosure of the region began in 1905 by the German scientist K. M . Kaufman, then followed by other research on intervals of the Greek Museum of Roman in Alexandria, the Coptic Museum in Cairo and others.
Modern monastery
Al -Shorouk began to wave the region again by Pope Kyrillos VI, as he started working with prayer between the ruins on the first day of the martyr after his ordination as a patriarch in 1959 AD.
Pope Kyrillos VI bought the area on which the modern monastery is completely adjacent to the archaeological area and the construction began again.
Pope Kyrillos VI returned part of the remains of the martyr Marmina, the wonders of his church in the mouth of the Gulf to the Monastery of Marmina in February in February 1962.
The archaeological disclosure operations began to take its regular characteristic since Pope Kyrillos VI established the current monastery, as the German Institute of Antiquities in Cairo began working since 1961 under the supervision of the German scientist Dr. Peter Grosman for a few months annually.
Pope Kyrillos VI handed over the secretariat of the Deira to his private student, the shirt Mina Ava Mina (who is the one who is delighted by Anba Mina, Bishop of the Monastery), to continue the work of Pope Kyrillos VI in the spiritual and structural construction of the monastery.
Pope Kyrillos VI laid the foundation stone for the Marmina Cathedral in 1961 AD, but the construction started in 1969 AD and the work is still ongoing. March 9, 1971 AD. His student, Father Mina Ava Mina, had received his will to be buried in the Monastery of Marmina.
His Holiness, Pope Shenouda III, preferred to implement the will of His Holiness Pope Kyrillos VI and transfer his pure body in a majestic celebration on November 24, 1972 AD.
Pope Shenouda III opened the Cathedral of Marmina in Outout, after the completion of the construction structure after the martyrdom of Marmina 17 Harator 1693 St. (November 26, 1976 AD), a Medal on this occasion, four new monks of the monastery.
Pope Shenouda III, with the poison of shirt Mina Ava Mina, head of the monastery, bishop on the monastery on the 17th of Bashc, 1696 St. (May 25, 1980 AD), in appreciation of the great responsibility that Pope Kyrillos VI left him.
UNESCO, 1979 AD, directed special attention to the ancient Abu Mina region, as it was approved within the 57 regions in the world - as a human heritage - it must be taken care of and preserved globally. In this regard, I published a book in 1982 AD, entitled (Alegacy for all) contains a brief description for each of these 57 The area as a historical registration for human civilization.
After the tournament of the great ink, Anba Mina on 12/11/1996, His Holiness, Pope Shenouda III, the 117th Patriarch, was ordained by the ordeal
In 2005, His Holiness, Pope Shenouda III, inaugurated the Greater Marmina Cathedral in the monastery, in the presence of many parents of the Holy Synod.
Pope Shenouda was visiting the monastery a lot, as he sometimes prayed the sheikh in the monastery, as well as the body of the martyr in his restoration.
On September 2, 2013, His Holiness, Pope Tawadros II, launched the first church on the name of the Great Saint Pope Kyrillos VI in the Monastery of Marmina
    </string>
    <string name="Abo_mena">
        Abu Mina archaeological area
Abu Mina archaeological area is located at the northern edge of the Western Sahara, which is called the Bedouins of the region (Abu Mina), which was in the past of a small village where the burial of St. Mina, and the region until the early Middle Ages was the most important Christian center for Hajj in Egypt and the region is located in the west of the city of Alexandria, near From the new city of Burj Al Arab, where there is a clear  desert that extends for a distance of 12 kilometers in the south to reach the antiquities area. This place was discovered in 1905 by the German archaeologist (Kaufman), where in the summer of 1907 he managed to reveal large parts of it. The Egyptian government recorded the Abu Mina region as an archaeological site according to Resolution No. 698 of 1956. In 1979, UNESCO decided to include the site on the World Heritage List. Thus, it became one of the most important historical places in Egypt.
Site
the threat
Abu Mina archaeological area is located next to the new city of Burj Al Arab, west of Alexandria, about 120 km away. It includes a group of Coptic antiquities, churches and monasteries, between 312 - 315 AD. The remains of the martyr "Marmina" were transferred to the monastery, and the first church was built in the Mariout region Between 320-325 AD, it is due to Emperor Constantine, it is worth noting that the region was subjected to extinction in the 13th century due to the raids of the Turks and the Persians in the region, and in the 14th century the remains of St. Marmina were transferred to the Marmina Church in the Ancient Egypt region.
Abu Mina archaeological area has become a threatened area since 2001 due to the high levels of groundwater and salts in the region and the Egyptian government has made several projects to protect and preserve the region as it has developed a plan to address the groundwater problem that includes a series of improvements to the health drainage system around the site of 1000 Fedda, including an area of ​​217 acres surrounding the main antiquities area, restoring tubes, wells and pumps to convert water from the site, and change the irrigation systems that farmers use in the vicinity Its main summer crops are corn and tomatoes, while they are planting wheat, barley and beets in this winter. The Ministry of Tourism and Antiquities has completed 80% of the project to replace, renew and raise the efficiency of the system of lowering the groundwater level in the ancient Abu Mina region, west of Alexandria.

    </string>

    <string name="bola">
        Monastery of St. Paula
The oldest monasteries of the world are located on a high plateau, in the bosom of the mountain on the Ras Gharib Road, Al -Za`fana, north of the Red Sea Governorate A year and a half ago, according to the precautionary and preventive measures in the face of the Corona virus\'s pandemic.
The Monastery of St. Paula, the oldest monasteries of the world, Bashar Abu Talib, head of the Captain of Tourist Guides in the Red Sea, said that the Monastery of Anba Paula is the oldest church and monasteries in the world, which dates back to the Byzantine ages, where it was established in the fourth century AD by the students of Anba «Anthony», and was built on A high plateau, and the monastery includes three churches, the first church of St. Martorius, the second Church of "Angel Michael" and then the Church of St. Paula, which is constructed over the cave in which St. Paula lived and the three archaeological churches, the oldest of which are the Church of St. Paula ancient.
The Monastery of St. Paula provides a climate for the monks, and Abu Talib adds that the monastery has tools one of the most important elements that provide a climate for the monks and their supplies, as it contains an eye of water, which is the origin of life, and it includes my Qalali for the old and modern monks, which are silos for housing, worship, and the two archaeological grain and archaeological tables The old and the modern, the press, and the circle of some sewers intended for monitoring in the pillars of the monastery, the basements, the duties, an archaeological table, and some mills, contemporary, water wells, then a large library with many drawings, manuscripts and artwork.
    </string>

    <string name="bishoy">
    Monastery of St. Bishoy
    History of the monastery
    In the end of the fourth century AD, the monastery was established under the leadership of St. Bishop Bishoy as a monastic gathering, and it includes the Church of St. Bishoy, the two monks, and a water well without walls.
    In the end of the fifth century AD during the rule of Emperor Zenon, the fort was established, which consists of three floors A - the first floor includes a water well, a grain mill, an oil press, and a thighs. B - The second floor has the entrance to the fort through a moving wooden bridge … It also has an oven and a church on the name of the Virgin Saint Mary. C - The third floor, which is the surface, and has a church on the name of the angel Michael, and two Maggara.
    In the ninth century AD, the current fences of the monastery were erected on an area of ​​about 3.
    In the fourteenth century AD, Pope Benjamin II, Patriarch 82, who was on the Patriarchate between 1327 - 1339 AD, made extensive restoration of the monastery due to the white termites that offered the church ceiling to collapse.
    The treasures of the monastery are the bodies of the existing saints, where there is the body of the great saint Anba Yishoy and St. Paula Al -Tamahi in one tube in the cabin in the first oak. The body of Pope Benjamin 52 is also in the Third Jose in the Church of the Great Saint Anba Yishoy. There is also the body of Pope Shenouda III 117 in the Mazar in the monastery garden.
    General Description
    The Monastery of St. Bishoy, the beloved of Christ, is the largest monasteries of the Natrun Valley, the area, in terms of the archaeological area without the added area, about two acres and 16 carats, and the monastery takes a quadruple shape determined by the surrounding walls. The entrance to the monastery is located at the western end of the northern wall, and it consists of the interior of a group of buildings, the most important of which is the fortress, and it is located in the northwestern corner of the monastery. In the southern part of the monastery, the Church of St. Bishoy and its accessories, which are represented in the "table", are located in the West; The structure of the Church of St. Benjamin is found in the north; And the Church of Abu Sakhrun; And the Church of Mar Gerges; And baptism in the south. As for the center of the monastery; The garden appears surrounding several buildings, from the northern side, my relatively modern said, which was built 60 years ago and is topped by the vacancy. The cemetery of the monks called the passion.

    Next to the southern wall, there is an ancient Qalali covered by cellars. In the southeastern corner of the monastery, there is both the kitchen, the old mill and the old bakery. In the north, there was a second row of Qalili, but it was destroyed, and the new hospitality house, which was built by the head of the monastery, was built by the Father Peter in 1926 (96 years ago). The monastery contains a library that is considered one of the smallest libraries of the monasteries, and the original library was in the fort, then it was transferred to its own building in the ground floor of the new hospitality house, and then it became in the room located above the hostess adjacent to the northern wall, until a huge library was created During the current Pope in 1989 (33 years ago). There were also many expansions in the monastery during the reign of Pope Shenouda II A museum store to preserve the effects of the monastery. The wall of the monastery and the fort and the Church of Anba Bishoy was restored under the supervision of the Egyptian Antiquities Authority.
    </string>

    <string name="Baramus">
        Al -Baramus Monastery
 Its history dates back to the fourth century AD, and its name is due to the name of the Monastery of the Virgin Mary "Permanel" in relation to the nomination of the ancient Church on the name of the Virgin Mary, which dates back to the time of St. Macarius the Great, where the first monastic group was formed in the Wadi al -Natrun region and the monastery is located on the northwestern end of Al -Natroun led on an area of ​​about 14 km to the west of the desert road "Cairo - Alexandria" at approximately 106 km.
The word Coptic word is meaning to the Romans relative to the spiritual saints Fiximos - and Rumadius.
This monastery is located, west of the Natron Valley Mallah, in a spot known in the ancient times as Netria. Five archaeological churches - are full of ancient artistic icons of an unique artistic nature.
The old section represents four churches in addition to some stores. As for the relatively recent section, it includes the Church of John the Baptist, the new hospitality palace, a library and a bakery, in addition to the burial of the monks (Tafus). This monastery retains the shelves of two famous monks.
The beginning of the Monastery of Al -Baramus
St. Macarius chose the place now known as the Monastery of Al -Barameos, dug for himself a cave and began to worship a lot. Soon his reputation came up and many of the murids who loved him with great love because of his fatherhood, wisdom and grace that was it. Saint Anba Makar stayed in this place for nearly twenty years until the Monastery of Al -Barramus was completed and the autistic who lived in the caves around the main church.
    </string>

    <string name="Deir_Al_Syriaan">
        Deir Al Syriaan
This monastery was built in the sixth century AD, and it was named by this name because many Syrian monks have erected over the centuries.
The main church in the monastery was attributed to the Virgin, and it contains great murals, and the structure is adorned with a dome decorated with scenes from the Bible, such as a scene depicting the birth of Christ.
In 1988 AD, a small fire in the monastery led to a mural from the twelfth century AD, under which a rare mural dating back to the year 950 AD appeared, and a representative of the scene of the celebration of the Virgin Mary.
Among the most important features of the Church are the gates of the Holy Mosque, which are decorated with images of Christ, the Virgin Mary, and other saints.
The Europeans have discovered a rare group of Syriac manuscripts in the Monastery Library during the nineteenth century AD, and it is currently present at the Vatican Library and other institutions. This group includes unique manuscripts from the oldest Greek texts of Aristotle, Euclid, and Graits.
The Syrian monastery built some women from Syria and the Monastery of Anba Bishoy was built in the name of one of the Christian saints, and the date of the establishment of the two monastery is exactly unknown.

These two days of the dwelling of the monks and the establishment of religious rituals of Orthodox Christians
The Syrian monastery has two main in the name of the Virgin Mary, the first of which is in the Byzantine style, and it is square in shape. Its entrance is located in the southwestern side. The other church follows the Bazalki style and consists of a bowl, two wings, a circular western side, a geese and structures. The Khor is separated from the plate by a wall that divides the church into two separate parts.
As for the Monastery of St. Bishoy, it has a major church bearing the name of St. Bishoy, which is in the Bazalki style. A large number of appendices and monks
    </string>

    <string name="antonios">Monastery of St. Anthony The Monastery of St. Anthony is the first monastery in the world and attributed its name to St. Anthony, the first monks in the world and the father of all monks. The Monastery of Anba Antonius is located at the foot of the tribal mountain of Galala in the Arab desert in Egypt, and the monastery area represents 18 acres, and the history of the monastery is due to the establishment of St. Anthony in his cave and the wrapping of a large number of monks around him, which called for the construction of a church in which he meets with the monks. The monastery includes a food store, a kitchen, and a minor, in an area of ​​no more than 3 acres contained in a wall of stone, and during the days of the rule of Emperor Justinian in 537 AD, the emperor doubled its area, after three acres became six of his benefits. The monastery was reconstructed after the ordination of the monk, Raphael, the Syriac Patriarch in October, 1525 AD, in the name of Pope Gabriel, the seventh of the 95th of Alexandria, so he sent 20 monks from the monastery of the Syriac, which was inhabited by 63 monks to the Monastery of Anba Antonius. The monastery includes 13 churches, namely: the Church of the Four Owners of the Non -Incarnated, Church of St. Anthony, Church of angels, Michael, Church The martyr Abanoub Walti, Rifaqa, Saint Paul\'s Simple Church, Church of the Rock, Church in the center of the mountain that appears from the great door of the monastery, the altar of St. Anthony.</string>

</resources>
